quizazz.com 2011-10-12

# Privacy Policy | Quizazz

We at Quizazz are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

Quizazz has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Quizazz's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

Quizazz strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Quizazz intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.

Third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Quizazz and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles:

**1\. Notice**  
Where Quizazz collects Personal Information on the web, we intend to post a purpose statement that explains why Personal Information will be collected. Quizazz does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Quizazz's behalf unless such transfer is legally required.

**2\. Choice**  
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Quizazz. The notice we intend to provide where Quizazz collects Personal Information on the Web should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of Quizazz's Web sites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services.

**3\. Security**  
Wherever your Personal Information may be held within Quizazz or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

**4\. Access/Accuracy**  
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Quizazz wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Quizazz should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to [contact@quizazz.com](mailto:contact@quizazz.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.

**Third Party Services**

Quizazz does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Quizazz's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Quizazz's policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

**Transfer of Business Assets**

As we continue to develop our business, we may be acquired, merge with another business, or acquire or buy other businesses or assets. In such transactions, both personally and non-personally identifiable information will likely be one of the transferred assets. 

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Quizazz is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Children**

Quizazz does not seek to collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If any child provides us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian may notify us and such information will be deleted from our records. 

**Commitment**

We are committed to privacy and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Quizazz's Web sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands.

**Your Consent**

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Quizazz's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where Quizazz collects Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@quizazz.com](mailto:privacy@quizazz.com).
